[Music]
step one
visit our manulife's website at
www.manulife.com dot my
step two mouse over services located in
the left tab
and click on file you will be directed
to the
how to make a claim page in this page
you will see the steps involved to make
a claim
beginning with types of claims that you
will be able to make
step 3. click on the type of claim you
intend to submit and download
the relevant forms you will then need to
complete the relevant forms and prepare
the required supporting documents
do take note of the important notes so
as to not overlook
any requirements before you submit your
claims
step 4 submit your completed forms and
documents to us
through the available options listed in
our website
that's it you've successfully submitted
your claims with us
with that your claim will be processed
within 7 to 10 working days
and you will be notified on the status
should you require further assistance in
regards to your claims
feel free to call our customer care line
or email us
[Music]
you